Hello friends welcome to policy plus
today we are comparing Tata Medicare
Premier and icac Elevate health
insurance policies before comparing
these two policies I request to all if
you want health insurance please call me
WhatsApp 934
936 to get medical insurance as per your
requirement I am providing all company
health insurance policies
first we are comparing eligibility age
tataa Medicare we can take up to 65 age
only but ICC elate we can take up to any
age that means anyone can take this
policy if you compare the summer sh
available range IC providing unlimited
coverage that means uh there is no limit
for insurance coverage
if you compare the room rate limit data
providing any room facility default but
ICC providing uh normal policy that
means basic policy providing single
standard AC room if you want you can
upgrade to any room Facility by uh
optional
Rider before continue this video I
request all if you not subscrib this
Channel Please Subscribe this channel
uh Bell button for future notification
update if you compare the pre and post
Hospital both plan providing same
coverage next we are comparing no claim
bonus benefit data will provide every
claim free year 50% and maximum up to
100% in ICC plan every claim free year
20% and maximum 100% in BC plan also you
have another option power booster Rider
if you take this Rider irrespective of
claim every year 100%
bonus uh restore benefit data provider
100% only with same person same inless
means 45 days delay with uh terms and
conditions ICC provide unlimited without
any terms and conditions
preexisting dis waiting period tataa 2
years
ICC 3 years but if you take the uh ABCD
Rider um Asma pressure cholesterol and
diabetic will cover from day one also
another uh problems you have the rider
to reduce the waiting Peri up to one
year also
the Civic surgery kidney stonea joint
replacement waiting period both plan uh
2 years but ICC another option available
to reduce to one
year next we are comparing maternity
cover tataa provide maximum up to 1.2
lakhs coverage and waiting period 48
month in
icac basic plan provide only Sate and
octar donor cover but if you want
maternity cover you have to take the
maternity cover optional Rider and we
will get maximum coverage up to 1 lakh
also newborn baby cover maximum up to 2
lakhs both plan providing martic surgery
coverage if you compare Katra limit both
plan and No
Limit if you compare the health checkup
benefit tataa will provide 1% of sumers
Maximum up to
25,000 in ic this is optional Rider uh
you will get benefit of 0.5% of sumers
or
5,000 in ambulance cover data will
provide uh per hospitalization 5,000 to
30,000 ICC actual they are
providing air ambulance benefit data
will provide up to 5 lakhs ICC provide
up to sumers suit but this is optional
Rider I treatment both plan providing a
coverage up to Summer
sh share accommodation coverage
if you stay in share accomodation during
ulation data will provide per day 0.25%
of sumers or maximum up to
2,000 in ic there is no coverage for
share accommodation uh if you want share
accommodation room you can inform the
company and will get premium discount
but if you choose other higher category
then C will
apply if you compare modern treatment
coverage both plan provide up to sumers
Shi
coverage if you compare Home Care
treatment tataa will provide this
facility only suers sh 75 lakhs and
above ICC this is optional Rider if you
take this Rider post hospital per day
2,000 for 10 days we will get
coverage for non-medical items like
gloves mask
sanitizer data provide up to sumers sh
but ICC uh there is no coverage in basic
plan if you want this cover you have to
take claim protector optional Rider then
we'll get coverage up to sumers
shot both plan providing and daycare
coverage up to Summer suit there is no
limit
domiciliary Hospital both plan this
facility
providing Argan donor coverage both plan
providing up to sumers sh
coverage if you compare extra benefit
both plan providing uh extra benefit if
you compare extra benefit in tataa you
will get common Sate with travel Global
coverage hearing head prolong hospital
highend diagnosis exal death Hospital
cash OPD Dental cover durable medical
equipment cover if you compare extra
benefit in ICC Elevate these are
optional Riders infinite care inflation
protector convence benefit TI
accommodation CH relief compensate visit
durable medical equipment cover personal
accident critical illness voluntary co-
payment NRI Advantage B fit worldwide
cover NRI
Advantage now we are comparing premium
up to 5 lakhs coverage Tata medical
premium around uh
20,700 IC Elevate basic premium
14,600 if you take
claim productor as a optional Rider and
the premium will be
15,700 if you compare uh 10 lakh
coverage premium will be uh 23,000 in
tata health insurance and 18,000 in ICC
Elevate please share suggestion and
feedback in comment section if you like
this video please click the Bell button
and uh subscribe this channel also share
to your friends for health insurance
please call 934 936 in WhatsApp see you
in next Insurance video thank you